https://www.kmtwaterjet.com/a-kmt-genuine-parts-privacy.aspx

KMT Privacy Policy
KMT PRIVACY POLICYThank you for visiting KMT Waterjet Systems, Inc.’s ("KMT") Internet web site ("Site") located at www.kmtwaterjet.com and
www.kmtgenuineparts.com. This Privacy Policy details certain policies implemented throughout KMT governing KMT's use of personally identifiable information about users of our Site.KMT recognize the importance of protecting personal information, and we protect personal information in an appropriate manner. KMT follows rules and regulations concerning the acquisition, use and supply, etc. of personal information, and based on them, handles personal information appropriately.To ensure the accuracy and security of personal information, KMT takes data/information security and control measures, thereby striving to prevent unauthorized access to personal information or prevent loss, destruction, falsification and leak of personal information.KMT may collect information regarding individual users' visit on KMT’s site. KMT may also use information regarding individual users in order to send product information and promotional material about KMT or its affiliates. Personal information collected on KMT's site may be stored and processed in Sweden or any other country in which KMT or its affiliates maintain facilities, and by using KMT’s site or services, you consent to any such transfer of information outside of your country.Respecting individual users'/customers' rights to information, KMT will comply with requests from individual users/customers involved for disclosure of their personal information, amendment, addition or deletion and erasing of the content of their personal information, and suspension of information supply to third parties, in accordance with the provisions of relevant laws. Privacy Policy UpdatesDue to the Internet's rapidly evolving nature, KMT may need to update this Privacy Policy from time to time. KMT updated Privacy Policy will be at http://www.kmtwaterjet.com/a-kmt-genuine-parts-privacy.aspxKMT may send registered users an email, so you are always aware of what personally identifiable information we may collect and how we may use this information. KMT encourages you to review this Privacy Policy regularly for any changes. Your continued use of this Site and/or continued provision of personally identifiable information to us will be subject to the terms of the then-current Privacy Policy.Information Collection and UseThis website is based on registering, and then entering in a user identification and password. If you purchase products, we may invite you to contact us with questions or comments or request information, provide us with feedback, or complete a registration form. Due to the nature of some of these activities, we will collect personally identifiable information, such as your name, contact data such as your address, email address, phone number, username, password, credit card number or other financial account information, and other contact information that you voluntarily transmit with your communication to us.We may use your personally identifiable information to register you to use our Site, deliver certain products, provide notices regarding products you have purchased, provide notices regarding products and/or services you might want to purchase in the future and verify your authority to enter our Site, and improve the content and general administration of the Site and our Services and for targeted advertising.CookiesWe may use small text files called cookies to improve overall Site experience. A cookie is a piece of data stored on the user's hard drive containing information about the user. Cookies generally do not permit us to personally identify you.Aggregate InformationThe Site may track the total number of visitors to our Site, the number of visitors to each page of our Site, browser type, and IP addresses, and we may analyze this data for trends and statistics in the aggregate, but such information will be maintained, used and disclosed in aggregate form only and it will not contain personally identifiable information. We may use such aggregate information to analyze trends, administer the Site, track users' movement, and gather broad demographic information for aggregate use.DisclosureWe may provide your personally identifiable information and the data generated by cookies and the aggregate information to the vendors and service agencies that we may engage to assist us in providing our Services to you. For example, we may provide your personally identifiable information to a credit card processing company to process your payment or to a marketing, research and/or advertising agency to send advertising to you on our behalf. Such third party entities may be restricted from further distributing your personally identifiable information and from using your personally identifiable information for commercial purposes and may be obligated to a written confidentiality agreement that is at least as protective of your personally identifiable information as the terms of this Privacy Policy. We will disclose your personally identifiable information if we reasonably believe we are required to do so by law, regulation or other government authority. We will not sell your personally identifiable information to any company or organization except we may transfer your personally identifiable information to a successor entity upon a merger, consolidation or other corporate reorganization in which KMT participates or to a purchaser of all or substantially all of KMT's assets to which this Site relates.Links to Third Party SitesThe Site may provide links to other Web sites or resources over which KMT does not have control ("External Web Sites"). Such links do not constitute an endorsement by KMT of those External Web Sites. You acknowledge that KMT is providing these links to you only as a convenience, and further agree that KMT is not responsible for the content of such External Web Sites. Your use of External Web Sites is subject to the terms of use and privacy policies located on the linked to External Web Sites.SecurityWe may employ procedural and technological security measures that are reasonably designed to help protect your personally identifiable information from loss, unauthorized access, disclosure, alteration or destruction. KMT may use secure socket layer, password protection, and other security measures to help prevent unauthorized access to your personally identifiable information.Correction/Updating Personally Identifiable InformationKMT provides you with the ability to review, correct and delete any of the personally identifiable information that you have provided to us. If you wish to review or correct any information you have provided to us, you may submit a request to us as the contact information below or access your account online.If you have any questions regarding this Privacy Policy please contact us via email at sales@kmtwaterjet.com.This Privacy Policy is effective as of: May 1, 2011GDPR DATA PROCESSING PRIVACY POLICY NOTICE (EU) >
